Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilm Legal Department records, 1916-1958 and undated RL.11718
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accounts, 1916-1958 and undated; 2
  - Lux Radio Theatre, 1952 (Reel 995)
    South Africa; budgets; coupons and contests; mail
  - Lux Radio Theatre, undated (Reel 994)
  - Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Mentholatum, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Mentholatum, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - Mentholatum, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Mentholatum, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Mentholatum, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Mentholatum, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Mentholatum, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Mentholatum, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Mentholatum, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Metropolitan Motor Coach, 1947 (Reel 873)
  - Metropolitan Motor Coach, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Michigan Hospital Service, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Michigan Hospital Service, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Michigan Hospital Service, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Michigan Hospital Service, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Michigan Hospital Service, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Michigan Medical Service, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Millers National Federation, 1946-1947 (Reel 873)
  - Millers National Federation, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Mobile Home Manufacturers Association, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Mobile Home Manufacturers Association, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Mobile Home Manufacturers Association, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Mobile Home Manufacturers Association, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Mosler Safe, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Murine, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Murine, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Murine, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Mutual Orange Distributors, 1945 (Reel 873)
  - Nashua Mills, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Nashua Mills, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - National Fisheries Institute, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - National Kids Day Foundation, undated (Reel 994)
  - National Peanut Council, 1945 (Reel 430)
  - National Peanut Council, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - National Shoe Institute, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - National Shoe Institute, 1948-1951 (Reel 873)
  - National Shoe Institute, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - National Trailways, 1950 (Reel 873)
  - NBC, 1945 (Reel 430)
  - NBC, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - New Holland Machine, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - New Holland Machine, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - New Holland Machine, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - New Holland Machine, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - New Holland Machine, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - New York Central Railroad, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - New York Central Railroad, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - New York Central System, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - New York Dress Institute, 1941 (Reel 315)
  - New York Dress Institute, 1941-1943 (Reel 873)
  - New York Subways, 1941-1945 (Reel 430)
  - New York Subways, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - New York Subways, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - New York Subways, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - New York Subways, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Noma, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Northam Warren, 1941 (Reel 375)
  - Northam Warren, 1941 (Reel 401)
  - Northam Warren, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - Northam Warren, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Northam Warren, 1945 (Reel 430)
  - Northam Warren, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Northam Warren--Federal Trade Commission, 1940 (Reel 283)
  - Northam Warren--Peggy Sage (Cutex, Odorono), 1941 (Reel 315)
  - Northeast Airlines, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Northern Trust, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Northern Trust, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Northrop Aircraft, 1945 (Reel 430)
  - Office Equipment Manufacturers Institute, 1951 (Reel 873)
  - Office Equipment Manufacturers Institute, undated (Reel 1013)
  - Office for Emergency Management Woman Power, undated (Reel 1013)
  - Old Fashion Products, undated (Reel 1013)
  - Old Virginia Packing, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Oneida, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Oneida, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Oneida, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Oneida, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Oneida, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Oneida, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Oneita Knitting Mills, 1952 (Reel 873)
  - Osborn Products, undated (Reel 1013)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1945 (Reel 430)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, undated (Reel 994)
  - Oxford University Press, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Oxford University Press, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Pacific Mills, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Pacific Mills, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Pacific Mills, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Pacific Mills, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Pacific Mills, 1954 (Reel 998)
    Claim files--Mrs. Vern Blum
  - Pacific Mills, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Pacific Mills, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Pan Am, 1945 (Reel 430)
  - Pan Am, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Pan Am, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Pan Am, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Pan Am, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Pan Am, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Pan Am, 1951 (Reel 994)
  - Pan Am, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Pan Am, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Pan Am, 1954 (Reel 998)
  - Pan Am, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Pan Am, 1955 (Reel 1012)
    Claim Files--Mrs. George Folster
  - Pan Am, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Pan Am, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Panagra, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Panagra, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Panama Pacific Line, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - Parker Pen, 1944-1945 (Reel 430)
  - Parker Pen, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Parker Pen, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Parker Pen, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Parker Pen, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Parker Pen, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Parker Pen, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Parker Pen, 1954 (Reel 994)
  - Parker Pen, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Penick & Ford, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Penick & Ford, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Penick & Ford, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Penick & Ford, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Penick & Ford, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Penick & Ford, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Penick & Ford, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1956-1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Pineapple Growers Association, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Pineapple Growers Association, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Planters Nut and Chocolate, 1932 (Reel 873)
  - Policy Commission of the Casualty Insurance Companies, 1950 (Reel 873)
  - Pond's Extract Co., 1926-1941 (Reel 414)
  - Pond's Extract Co., 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Pond's Extract Co., 1945 (Reel 430)
  - Pond's Extract Co., 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Pond's Extract Co., 1947-1948 (Reel 743)
  - Pond's Extract Co., 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Pond's Extract Co., 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Pond's Extract Co., 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Pond's Extract Co., 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Pond's Extract Co., 1955 (Reel 998)
    Claim files--Candle Light
  - Pond's Extract Co., undated (Reel 994)
    Training; Argentina
  - Port of New York Authority, 1950 (Reel 873)
  - Publit Utilities Commission, City and County of San Francisco, 1950 (Reel 873)
  - Puget Sound Navigation, 1945 (Reel 873)
  - Purolator, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Purolator, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Purolator, 1953-1954 (Reel 996)
  - Purolator, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Purolator, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Putnam Trust, 1948-1949 (Reel 744)
  - Quaker Oats, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Quaker Oats, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Quaker Oats, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Quaker Oats, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Quaker Oats, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Radio Distributing, undated (Reel 1013)
  - RCA, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - RCA, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - RCA, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - RCA, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - RCA, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - RCA, 1948 (Reel 994)
  - RCA, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - RCA, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - RCA, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - RCA, 1954 (Reel 994)
  - Reader's Digest Association, 1945 (Reel 430)
  - Reader's Digest Association, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Reader's Digest Association, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Reader's Digest Association, 1948 (Reel 994)
  - Reader's Digest Association, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Reader's Digest Association, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Real Gold Citrus, 1949 (Reel 873)
  - Religion in American Life, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Religion in American Life, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Religion in American Life, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1945 (Reel 430)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - RKO Pictures, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - RKO Pictures, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Robert A. Johnston, 1956-1957 (Reel 1010)
  - Rystan, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Rystan, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Rystan, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Safeway Stores, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Safeway Stores, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Safeway Stores, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Safeway Stores, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Safeway Stores, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Safeway Stores, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Safeway Stores, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Safeway Stores, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Safeway Stores, undated (Reel 1013)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 1949 (Reel 873)
  - Sarfert Hosiery Mills, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Schlitz, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Schlitz, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Scott Paper, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Scott Paper, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - Scott Paper, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Scott Paper, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Scott Paper, 1953-1954 (Reel 994)
    Television: My Little Margie Vol. 1-4
  - Scott Paper, 1953-1955 (Reel 996)
  - Scott Paper, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Scott Paper, 1955 (Reel 1012)
    Claim Files--My Little Margie
  - Scott Paper, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Scott Paper, 1956 (Reel 1010)
    Television--Father Knows Best vol. 1-2
  - Scott Paper, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Scott Paper, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Scott Paper--Federal Trade Commission, 1940 (Reel 283)
  - Scranton Lace, 1942 (Reel 375)
  - Scranton Lace, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Scranton Lace, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Scranton Lace, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Scripto, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Sears Roebuck, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Sears Roebuck, undated (Reel 994)
    Liberty Broadcasting System
  - Seth Thomas Clock, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Seth Thomas Clock, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Seven-Up, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - Seven-Up, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Seven-Up, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Seven-Up, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Seven-Up, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Seven-Up, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Seven-Up, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Seven-Up, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Seven-Up, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Seven-Up, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Seven-Up, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1942 (Reel 375)
    Immunization advertisements
  - Shell Chemical, 1953 (Reel 994)
    Bill Weevil Blues
  - Shell Chemical, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Shell Oil, 1939 (Reel 283)
  - Shell Oil, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - Shell Oil, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Shell Oil, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - Shell Oil, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Shell Oil, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Shell Oil, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Shell Oil, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Shell Oil, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Shell Oil, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Shell Oil, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Shell Oil, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Shell Oil, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Shell Oil, undated (Reel 995)
  - Shell Oil--Federal Trade Commission, 1940 (Reel 283)
  - Skol, 1937-1938 (Reel 1008)
    Federal Trade Commission investigation
  - Skol, 1943 (Reel 430)
  - Skol, 1944-1945 (Reel 431)
  - Skyway International Luggage, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Southeastern Trailways, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Southern Trailways, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Squibb, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Squibb, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Squibb, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Squibb, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Squibb, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Standard Brands, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - Standard Brands, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Standard Brands, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - Standard Brands, 1946 (Reel 739)
  - Standard Brands, 1946 (Reel 739)
    Deferred compensation payments, Edgar Bergen
  - Standard Brands, 1946 (Reel 740)
  - Standard Brands, 1946 (Reel 740)
  - Standard Brands, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Standard Brands, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Standard Brands, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Standard Brands, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Standard Brands, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Standard Brands, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Standard Brands, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Standard Brands, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - Standard Brands, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Standard Brands--One Man's Family, 1936 (Reel 375)
  - Standard Brands--Radio, 1939 (Reel 283)
  - Standard Brands--Radio, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - Standard Brands--Victor Lawson claim, Fleischmann's swim book, 1940-1941 (Reel 315)
  - Staze, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Story-A-Day, 1952 (Reel 873)
  - Sunset Magazine, undated (Reel 1013)
  - Swift, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - Swift, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Swift, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - Swift, 1946 (Reel 740)
  - Swift, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Swift, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Swift, 1948-1949 (Reel 744)
  - Swift, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Swift, 1952 (Reel 995)
    Red Foley Keepsake Album
  - Swift, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Swift, 1954-1955 (Reel 996)
  - Swift, 1954-1956 (Reel 998)
    Swift Show Wagon vol. 1-3
  - Swift, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - Swift, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Swift, undated (Reel 994)
    Red Foley Keepsake album
  - Sylvania Electric Products, 1954-1955 (Reel 996)
  - Sylvania Electric Products, 1954-1955 (Reel 998)
  - Sylvania Electric Products, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Sylvania Electric Products, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Sylvania-Corning Nuclear, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Textron, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - Textron, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Textron, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - Textron, 1946 (Reel 740)
  - Textron, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Textron, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Textron, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Thomas Edison, 1956 (Reel 1010)
  - Thompson Products, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Thompson Products, 1948 (Reel 873)
  - Todd Shipyards, 1942 (Reel 873)
  - Trailer Coach Manufacturers Association, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Trico Products, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Trico Products, 1955 (Reel 998)
  - Trico Products, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - Trico Products, 1957 (Reel 1010)
  - Truck Rentals of New York, 1950 (Reel 873)
  - Tuna Research Foundation, 1952-1953 (Reel 995)
  - Tuna Research Foundation, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1946 (Reel 740)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1955 (Reel 998)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - U.S. Information Agency (USIA), 1955 (Reel 1011)
  - U.S. Information Agency (USIA), 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - U.S. Lines, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - U.S. Lines, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - U.S. Lines, 1956 (Reel 1012)
    Claim Files--Who's Who
  - U.S. Marine Corps, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - U.S. Marine Corps, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - U.S. Marine Corps, 1955 (Reel 998)
  - U.S. Marine Corps, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - U.S. Marine Corps, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - U.S. Playing Card, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - U.S. Playing Card, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - U.S. Playing Card, 1946 (Reel 740)
  - U.S. Playing Card, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - U.S. Playing Card, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - U.S. Playing Card, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - U.S. Playing Card, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - Union Central Life Insurance, undated (Reel 1013)
  - United Artists, 1942-1949 (Reel 873)
  - United Church Canvass, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - United Cut Flower, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - United Cut Flower, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - United Cut Flower, 1946 (Reel 740)
  - United Medical Service, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - United Medical Service, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - United Medical Service, 1955 (Reel 998)
  - Upholstery Leather Group, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Vimms--Frank Sinatra contract, 1944 (Reel 375)
  - W.F. Young, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - W.F. Young, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - W.F. Young, 1946 (Reel 740)
  - W.F. Young, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - W.F. Young, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - W.F. Young, 1948 (Reel 743)
  - W.F. Young, 1948 (Reel 994)
    Inhaler, Absorbine Jr.
  - W.F. Young, 1949 (Reel 745)
  - W.F. Young, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - W.F. Young, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - W.F. Young, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - W.F. Young, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - W.F. Young, 1955 (Reel 998)
  - W.F. Young, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - W.F. Young, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - W.F. Young--Federal Trade Commission, 1941 (Reel 315)
  - Ward Baking, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - Ward Baking, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Ward Baking, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - Ward Baking, 1946 (Reel 740)
  - Ward Baking, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Ward Baking, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Ward Baking, 1949 (Reel 744)
  - Ward Baking, 1949 (Reel 745)
  - Ward Baking, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Ward Baking, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Ward Baking, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Ward Baking, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Ward Baking, 1955 (Reel 998)
  - Ward Baking, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - Ward Baking, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Washington State Apple Commission, 1936-1947 (Reel 873)
  - Washington State Apple Commission, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Washington State Apple Commission, 1949 (Reel 745)
  - Washington State Apple Commission, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Washington State Apple Commission, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Washington State Dairy Products Commission, 1951 (Reel 873)
  - Webb Young Trader, 1949 (Reel 745)
  - Weco Products, 1943 (Reel 401)
  - Weco Products, 1944 (Reel 430)
  - Weco Products, 1945 (Reel 431)
  - Weco Products, 1946 (Reel 740)
  - Weco Products, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Weco Products, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Weco Products, 1949 (Reel 745)
  - Weco Products, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Weco Products, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Weco Products, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Weco Products, 1955 (Reel 998)
  - Weco Products, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - Weco Products, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Wells Organization, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - Wells Organization, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Western Union, 1946 (Reel 740)
  - Western Union, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Western Union, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Western Union, 1949 (Reel 745)
  - Western Union, 1950 (Reel 746)
  - Whizzer Motor, 1947 (Reel 741)
  - Whizzer Motor, 1948 (Reel 742)
  - Whizzer Motor, 1949 (Reel 745)
  - Wine Advisory Board, 1939-1940 (Reel 283)
  - Wine Advisory Board, 1949 (Reel 745)
  - Wine Advisory Board, 1953 (Reel 995)
  - Wine Advisory Board, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Wine Advisory Board, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Wine Advisory Board, 1955 (Reel 998)
  - Wine Advisory Board, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - Wool Bureau, 1954 (Reel 997)
  - Wool Bureau, 1955 (Reel 996)
  - Wool Bureau, 1955 (Reel 998)
  - Wool Bureau, 1956 (Reel 1011)
  - Wool Bureau, 1957 (Reel 1008)
  - Wrigley, 1931-1940 (Reel 873)
  - Wrigley--Melody Farm, 1940 (Reel 375)
  - York Knitting Mills (Canada), 1947 (Reel 741)
    Kroy Unshrinkable Woolens
  - York Knitting Mills (Canada), 1948 (Reel 742)
- Advertisers Liability Insurance, 1941-1953; 3
  - Ballantine--"After the Ball" lyrics, 1943-1945 (Reel 283)
  - Ballantine--Baby Rose Marie claim, 1940s (Reel 283)
  - Ford--George Brand Studio, "Stars of the Future", 1945 (Reel 283)
  - Ford--HVN Service Corporation Transfilm: Ford Motor Company Travelogue, 1945-1946 (Reel 283)
  - Ford--Joseph Kane claim, "Famous Ford Firsts", 1945 (Reel 283)
  - Ford--Walter Rogers claim, 1945 (Reel 283)
  - General Cigar--Paul Gardner claim, "White Owl Night Owl", 1945 (Reel 283)
  - Kraft--Lew Brown claim, Phil Silvers sketch on Kraft Music Hall, 1944 (Reel 283)
  - Libby McNeil & Libby--Paul Rand claim, 1944 (Reel 283)
  - Lux Radio Theatre--Tom Howard claim, 1943 (Reel 283)
  - Old Gold "What's New" radio program--Paul Specht, Sheppard Barkley claim, 1941 (Reel 283)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass--Mrs. Roark Bradford claim, "John Henry", 1945 (Reel 283)
  - Shell Oil--H.P.C. Keuls (Pearl & Shell), 1945 (Reel 283)
  - Standard Brands--Frank Fay, 1944 (Reel 283)
  - Standard Brands--Joseph Graydon claim, 1945 (Reel 283)
  - Standard Brands--Taylor v. Goldsmith (Henry Aldrich, "What a Life"), 1946 (Reel 283)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation--Rufus and Jane Cupper claim, 1945 (Reel 283)
  - Vol. 3, 1951-1953 (Reel 998)
  - Wrigley--Lt. Col. Frank O'Brien claim, 1945 (Reel 283)
  - Wrigley--Samuel Brodsky claim, 1945 (Reel 283)
- Edward G. (E.G.) Wilson Papers, 1952-1955 and undated; 4
  - Chronological files, 1952 (Reel 903)
  - Chronological files, 1955 (Reel 1011)
  - Detroit Office Operating Committee, 1954-1955 (Reel 1011)
  - General files, undated (Reel 1013)
  - Personal correspondence, 1955 (Reel 1011)
  - Private papers, undated (Reel 65)
  - Robert Farr, 1955 (Reel 1011)
  - Story-A-Day, 1952-1953 (Reel 995)